（潤一郎）これは間違いない。
But there's no doubt.
（潤一郎）僕は
彼女の遺体を確認したんだ。→
I made sure it was her body.
彼女は
孤島で　樽と共に死んでいる。
She died on an island, next to a barrel.
（潤一郎）ひと月半ほど前かな→
It was about a month and a half ago.
左門さんたちから連絡があってね→
I heard from Samon and the others.
So I returned to the Kusaribe family manor.
鎖部の本家に行ったんだよ。
（潤一郎・回想）((潤一郎です))
（左門）((入れ))
It's me, Junichiro.
Come in.
（左門）((よく来てくれた　潤一郎))
Thank you for coming, Junichiro.
Why did you call me here?
((姫様を亡き者にした))
I have disposed of the princess.
Episode 6
The Paradox
of the Skull
（潤一郎）
((はじまりの樹の加護を→
How'd you manage that, when Hakaze has the Tree of Genesis's full protection?
最大限に受ける葉風ちゃんを
どうやって？))
Not to mention that killing her would require
((そもそも　彼女を殺すなんて
理を　犯しすぎです))
a violation of logic that would be too severe.
Who knows what might happen...
((賭けだったよ。→
It was a risk.
姫様を薬で眠らせ
あの樽に入れて→
I used medicine to put the princess to sleep,
placed her in that barrel,
孤島に置き去りにした))
and then stranded her on an island.
((加護が十分であれば
脱出することも不可能ではない))
It isn't impossible for her to escape, given sufficient assistance.
((だが　はじまりの樹は
まだ完全に目覚めてはいない))
But the Tree of Genesis has yet to fully wake.
（潤一郎）((自然の理が
彼女を殺すかどうか→
So you gambled to see if nature's own logic
サイコロを振りましたか…))
would kill her.
((確かに　それは
あなたが　理を犯したことに→
You may not be deemed guilty of violating logic, then.
ならないかもしれません))
（左門）((昨日　樽と共に→
Yesterday,
島から遺体を回収した))
I went to retrieve both barrel and corpse from the island.
（左門）
((鳥や磯の生物に食われたのか→
I'm uncertain if an animal on the island ate her,
but she'd already been reduced to bones.
姫様は　すでに骨と化していたよ))
（不破真広）骨だけで
よく葉風と確信できたな。
I'm surprised you could ascertain Hakaze's identity from bones alone.
（潤一郎）頭蓋骨がね
葉風ちゃんだったんだよ。
The skull was Hakaze's.
あの子の頭の形　きれいだったから。
I always did think she had a nicely shaped head.
直感的に分かったんだ→
It was instinctual,
これは葉風ちゃんだってね。
but I knew it was Hakaze.
((潤一郎　一族は　これから→
Junichiro,
the clan will now take definite steps to wake the Tree of Exodus.
絶園の樹復活を　本格的に進める))
((そうですか))
I see.
((僕は　魔法を使えませんし→
I can't use magic,
なるべく中立でいるように
先代に遺言されています))
and the previous leader ordered me to stay as neutral as possible.
((ああ。　だから
お前が復活を支持すれば→
Yes.
That's why if you were to order the Tree of Exodus's awakening,
一族も　一層まとまるのだがな))
it would be much more likely to unite the clan.
So you really killed Hakaze?
((本当に　葉風ちゃんを
殺したんですか？))
What good would it do me to lie?
It just doesn't sound like something you'd do.
（潤一郎）((あなたらしくない手を
とったものだなと。→
直接　殺さないとはいえ→
Even though you did not kill her directly,
the potential consequences are unclear.
やはり　あとで何が起こるか
読みきれないのに))
((当面　弔っている暇はない))
There is no time to mourn her passing.
((骨は　本家で預かるが→
The bones will be placed at the head house,
供養は頼む))
but I leave the memorial service to you.
（潤一郎）葉風ちゃんが　一族で
孤立していたのは知ってたけど→
I knew Hakaze felt isolated within the clan,
まさか
お弔いまで任されるなんて。
but I never thought I'd be in charge of her funeral.
It appears that you believe Hakaze to be alive.
葉風ちゃんが
生きてると思ってるみたいだね。
あれが　殺して死ぬヤツか？
You think she's the type to die, even if killed?
I'd have to agree,
同感だ。
はじまりの樹の加護もあるし。
not to mention the Tree of Genesis's protection.
メッセージを瓶に入れて
島から流すだけで→
I believe she'd be lucky enough
to send a message in a bottle
外部との接触に成功しそうな
強運な子だ。
and establish contact with the outside world.
（滝川吉野・心の声）≪鋭い≫
He's perceptive.
I won't ask any more questions.
（潤一郎）まあ　詮索はよそう。→
I was merely asked to hold on to that.
僕は　それを
預かるように頼まれただけだ。→
何をすべきかは
君たちの方が分かってるんだろ？
I'm sure you two know what has to be done.
And you're okay with this?
お前　それでいいのか？
（潤一郎）えっ？
Huh?
You know something messed up is happening, right?
何か　やばいことが起こってるのは
気付いてんだろ？
これが　僕にできる精一杯。
This is the best I can do.
それに…。
それに？
Not to mention that...
What?
いや
君らに言うべきことでもないか。
Nevermind.
It's nothing worth bothering you with.
はぁ…　行くぞ　吉野。
Let's go, Yoshino.
あっ…　おじゃましました。
Thank you for your time.
ピッピッピッ
あぁ～あ…　ああ～。
Who the hell was that guy?
あの野郎　何者だ？
（葉風）先代の遠い縁者で→
He's the last leader's distant relative,
幼いときに両親を亡くして
一族に引き取られた。→
who lost his parents at a young age and was adopted into the clan.
だから　魔法も使えんし
権限も　特に与えられていないが→
Thus, he can't use magic,
nor was he given any real power.
But the previous leader trusted him,
先代に信頼されていたこともあって
一族では知られている。
and everyone in the clan knows him.
Sounds like you let your guard down with him...
（通信）
えらく気を許してたみたいだな。→
He sure as hell sounded affectionate about you.
「葉風ちゃん」って　なんだよ。
権限がないだけに→
Because of his position,
私を姫として敬う必要もないと→
he wasn't really required to treat me as the princess.
So I was like a little sister.
まあ　妹のようにだな…。
And you were happy having him pat you on the head.
頭なでてもらって
喜んでたってわけかよ。
（葉風・通信）喜んでなどおらん！
（乗客）ん？
I never said I was happy about that!
ともかく　信用はできるんですね？
Anyway, we can trust him, right?
できる。　潤兄さんだけは
うそをつかんし　裏切らん。
Yes.
Junichiro wouldn't lie or betray me.
Oh...
へえ～。
じゃあ　その潤兄さんが→
Then why did he say you were dead?
お前が死んでると言ったのは？
分からん。　勘の鋭い人だし→
I'm not sure.
He's a very perceptive person,
軽率な判断をするとも思えない。
and I doubt he'd jump to any baseless conclusions.
なのに　骨を私のものとした…。
However, he believed the bones were mine...
なぜだ。
Why?
単純に考えれば
彼が左門と手を組んで→
If we think about it simply,
is it possible that he's joined Samon and is trying to trick us?
僕らをだまそうとしている？
なら　あの場で
俺らを捕まえれば済む話だ。
Then he could have just captured us there.
And we have proof that she's alive.
それに　生きている証拠はある。
リアルタイムに
その人形でつながってるのを→
Maybe it's because he didn't know about the doll and that we're connected in real time.
知らなかったから？
にしても　うそとしちゃ苦しいぞ。
But if what he said was a lie, it was a pretty weak one.
葉風が死んでるって証拠は
あいつの証言だけだ。
His word is our only proof of Hakaze's death.
なら　左門は　ただ一族全体に→
So maybe Samon wants the whole clan
葉風さんが死んでいると
思わせたかった…　とかは？
to believe Ms. Hakaze is dead?
What good would that do?
思わせてどうする？
だいたい　堅実な左門が→
Also, knowing how thorough Samon is,
偽造した骨ごときで
だまし通せるとは思わんだろう。
I doubt he'd actually believe he could fool Junichiro with fake bones.
（通信）でも
あいつは　その頭蓋骨一つで→
But he was pretty certain that you were dead,
just by looking at the skull.
お前が死んだと確信したぜ。
だから分からん→
That's why I don't really know.
それが
本当に私の骨でないかぎり。
Unless those were my bones somehow...
What would that make you? A ghost?
それとも　お前　幽霊か何かか？
There are no such things as ghosts.
（葉風・通信）
幽霊など　この世におらん。
True.
そうだな
そんな不合理なものはいねぇな。
Something that absurd wouldn't exist...
Considering what's been going on,
≪それを言うなら
この全部が不合理だよ≫
"absurd" defines almost everything so far.
真広！　蝶だ！
何!?　うっ…。
Mahiro! Butterflies!
What?
This isn't good.
ひどいな。　あれが　絶園の果実か。
So that's what a fruit of Exodus looks like.
この辺も　黒鉄病の影響範囲に？
Now this area's within reach of the Black Iron Syndrome.
≪（夏村）潤一郎殿。
Mr. Junichiro.
そのまま走れ。　でないと→
Keep driving,
or we won't be able to escape this area.
この辺りから出られなくなるぞ。
（運転手）なっ　何が…。
Wh-What's...
いいから
前向いて　アクセル踏んでろ。
It doesn't matter.
Just put your foot on the gas and drive!
そんで　あとで　ありがたがれ
俺らの近くにいなかったら→
And be thankful later.
If you weren't around us,
今頃　金属になってたってな。
（運転手）うっ…。
you'd have turned into metal by now.
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか？
左門のヤツ　相当　焦ってるな。
みたいだね。
Seems Samon's getting pretty impatient.
Looks that way.
Hakaze, we're shelving the whole bone issue for now.
葉風　骨の問題は棚上げだ。
答えがなんであれ
復活を邪魔すりゃ勝ちだろ。
Whatever the answer,
if we can stop the awakening, we win.
Right?
（通信）違うか？
よし　許可する。
左門のところへ向かえ。→
Very well.
I give you permission to head to Samon's location.
We'll end this quickly!
（通信）一気にたたくぞ。
へっ。
久しぶりだね。
（夏村）よくご無事で。
It's been a while.
I'm glad to see that you're well.
先代からもらった
魔具があったから。
I have a talisman from the previous leader.
We're currently at a point
（夏村）もはや　状況は　後戻り
できぬところまで来ています。
from which we can no longer return.
Please consider dropping your neutrality and joining our side.
中立などと言われずに
我らのところに来られませんか？
Emotionally, I'd have to say I'm on Hakaze's side.
心情的には
葉風ちゃんの味方だけどね。
Well, then we'll have to do this by force.
では　力ずくでも…。
う～ん…　左門さんは
放っておけって言うと思うけど。
I'm pretty sure Samon would tell you to leave me alone...
それは　後ほど確かめます！→
I shall verify that later!
（潤一郎）魔法使いでもない僕が
どうして　左門さんから→
Do you know why Samon acknowledges me, even though I can't use magic?
一目置かれていると思う？
Magic? No...
≪魔法？　いや…≫
（潤一郎）
ともかく　僕は　手を貸す気はない。
Regardless, I have no intention of helping you.
それに　これ
今日だけで　何人死んでる？
Besides, today alone, how many have died?
しかし　ご存じのはずです→
However, I'm sure that you are aware
本当に恐ろしいのは
そんなことではないと。
that the real threat is far worse.
≪確かに。　あの二人は
知らされていないのだろうな→
It's probable that those two haven't been told...
絶園の樹より→
That it's the Tree of Genesis and Hakaze, not the Tree of Exodus,
むしろ　葉風ちゃんと
はじまりの樹の方が→
この世を
崩壊させかねないことを≫
which are more likely to destroy the world.
さて　どうする？
Now what?
歩くしかないだろうね。
I guess we'll have to walk...
あっさり言ってくれるぜ。
Thanks for stating the obvious.
いいな？
今来た道を戻ろうなんて→
Listen...
Don't even think about returning the way we came.
考えるなよ。
えっ？
カチンカチンになりたきゃ
別にかまわないけどな。
Unless you'd rather be turned into metal.
潤一郎さんの話をしてるときの
葉風さん→
Ms. Hakaze sounded pretty girly when talking about Junichiro.
ちょっと乙女だったね。
（葉風・通信）なんだと!?
What was that?!
そういう話は
こいつが寝てるときにしろ。
You should wait to say those things when she's asleep...
（葉風・通信）
寝てるときでもするな！→
Don't say things like that when I'm asleep, either!
First of all, Junichiro and I are...
第一
潤兄さんと私は　そのような…。
（２人）はははっ。
（葉風・通信）何がおかしい！
ピッピッ　ピッピッピッ
彼女にか？
Texting your girlfriend?
Eh? Yeah.
If you're that worried about her, just go to her.
そんなに心配なら
一緒にいてやりゃいいじゃねぇか。
知ってたか？
愛花に彼氏がいたってうわさ。
Did you hear the rumor that Aika had a boyfriend?
いや…。
Nope.
いつだったかの
バレンタインデーに→
She bought someone Valentine's Day chocolates one year.
あいつ　チョコ買ってた。
あっ…。
どうかしたか？
いや…。
Something wrong?
No.
ほら　彼女　そういうの
あげたりするような子に→
I was just surprised because she didn't seem the type to give someone chocolates.
見えなかったから。
≪まずい…　顔に出た？≫
Not good.
That totally showed on my face.
ほんとに
分かってねぇんだよな　お前→
You really don't get her, do you?
愛花のこと。
Aika, I mean.
≪信じたのか？　これで≫
So he believed me...
なんで鎖？
ふっ　特別だからじゃねぇか？
What's with the chain?
Maybe because it's special?
よう　葉風。　特製の魔具って→
Hey, Hakaze.
Why is the special talisman such a blatant weapon?
なんで　こう
がっちりした武器なんだ？
When Kusaribe magic offers the Tree of Genesis a lethal weapon,
鎖部の魔法は
殺傷能力の高い武器を→
はじまりの樹に捧げると
強い魔法を使いやすい傾向にある。
it tends to make it easier to use powerful magic.
Isn't that a contradiction?
矛盾してないか？　それ。
この世の理を守る　はじまりの樹が
破壊的な武器を→
Why would a Tree that's supposed to protect this world
desire destructive weapons?
（通信）望むってのは。
そうか？
You think so?
はじまりの樹が　ことごとく
兵器を吸収し　塵とすれば→
If the Tree of Genesis absorbs the whole weapon, destroying it,
戦争は激減するであろう？
wouldn't that reduce conflict?
Isn't that a step toward preserving the world's equilibrium?
世の安定は
一層　守られると思わんか？
ふん　世の安定か…。
The world's equilibrium, huh?
俺には　どうでもいいことだな。
Not that any of this matters to me...
≪確かに　真広の中で→
It's true that
to Mahiro, the world has been out of joint
世の中の関節が
外れてしまったのは→
昨日今日の話ではない≫
since long before any of this.
≪あの日以来　ずっと…≫
Ever since that day.
吉野。
Yoshino.
囲まれてる。
えっ？
We're surrounded.
魔具は持っているよな？
You have a talisman, right?
うっ！
まずい！
This is bad!
くっ！　これじゃあ
魔法もへったくれもねぇ！
At this rate, magic won't do us any good!
放せ！　放せ！
Let go! Let go of me!
吉…　うっ！
Yoshi—
（山本）少し気が咎める？
Are you feeling at all guilty?
彼に秘密で
私と取り引きしてたこと。
About the fact that we had a secret deal behind his back?
別に。　真広には　もっと→
Not really.
I've been keeping an even bigger secret from Mahiro.
大きな隠し事をしているわけだし。
True... I suppose you have a point.
そうか　そうなるわね。
だけど　なんか激しすぎない？→
However, don't you think it's a little extreme?
妹さんへの彼の気持ち。
How intensely he feels for his sister?
そうですか？
Is it?
（山本）兄妹っていっても　血は
つながってなかったわけでしょ？
Even though they were siblings,
they weren't blood relations, right?
知ってたんですか？
You knew?
（愛花）((あなたは　私と→
What relationship do you want to have with me,
どうなりたいんですか？　真広))
Mahiro?
((真広))
Mahiro.
（葉風・通信）真広！　真広！
Mahiro!
黙れ…。
Shut... up.
吉…　うっ！
Yoshi—
くそっ…　吉野！
（葉風・通信）真広!?→
Damn it!
Mahiro!
Yoshino!
どうした　真広！
What happened, Mahiro?
たぶん　真広は
自分でも分かってませんよ→
I don't think Mahiro himself knows
愛花ちゃんに抱いていたものが
どういう感情に基づく衝動で→
the basis for his feelings toward Aika.
なんと呼ばれる思いなのか…。
Or what exactly those feelings were.
It was obvious to everyone else, though.
でも　はたから見れば
丸分かりなんですけどね。
後をつける気になれば
楽ですよね→
It'd be easy to follow us if he wanted...
これだけ大仰な一団が
お付きで囲んでいれば。
Considering the size of our escort.
Do you think he'll follow?
（山本）彼　追ってくるかしら？
どうでしょう？　あっ。
Who knows?
Is that it?
あれですか？
まだ富士山麓まではありますよね。
Aren't we still a bit far from Mt. Fuji's base?
（山本）
君に会わせたい人がいるのよ。
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
≪ガチャ
（早河）やあ　無事で何より。
Hey, I'm glad you're safe.
You say that rather easily,
つらっと言うのね
人をやばい所に送り込んどいて。
considering the dangerous place you sent me to.
君を信頼している。
I believe in you.
I'm holding back the tears.
（山本）涙が出そう。　彼。
Here he is.
（早河）情報提供に感謝する。
あっ…。
Thank you for all the information you've provided us.
紹介するわ。　早河巧。
I'll introduce you.
This is Hayakawa Takumi,
黒鉄病対策本部長補佐。
Assistant Director of the Black Iron Syndrome Countermeasures Force.
私の古い友人でもある。
そのよしみで→
He's also an old friend.
Because we go back a long way,
公には　やりづらい仕事を
やってもらっている。
I ask her to do work that'd be difficult through official channels.
Basically, I'm a volunteer.
（山本）
ボランティアみたいなものね。→
But I have clearance to use weapons.
銃器の使用許可も　もらえたし。
あなたが　この軍を？
So you're the head of this army?
私の祖父が　鎖部一族の長と
友人だったということもあり→
Partially because my grandfather was friends with a past head of the Kusaribe clan.
魔法が　社会的な問題を
起こしたときには→
It became necessary to form a secret government organization
to respond swiftly in case of incidents where magic led to social problems.
秘密裏に　素早く動ける
国家的組織を作る必要があった。
そうは言っても
後手後手に回ることも多くてね。
However it isn't unusual for us to be behind on things.
In truth, we're somewhat puzzled
（早河）常識の範囲から
逸脱したことばかり起きて→
by all these illogical events.
戸惑っているのは確かだ。
だが　それを　手をこまねいて
見ているわけにはいかない。→
But we can't just stand idly by and watch.
我々は
魔法使いに　戦争を仕掛ける。
We'll wage war on the mages.
War?
戦争？
この現実離れした事象が→
These surreal events
are having such impact on the very fabric of society
だが　確実に
あらゆる社会構造に影響を与え→
時には
消滅させようとさえしている。→
that they look like they are about to destroy it.
We have no choice but to strike back using force.
もはや　武力で抗する以外にない。
（山本）ま…　まあ
急に大きな話をしても…。
Hey, no need to tackle a weighty topic so soon.
あっ　これ　頼まれていたもの。
Oh, here.
The thing you requested.
ああ　助かります。
Thanks, this will help.
じゃあ　お返しです。
And I'll give you this in return.
これで　私も魔法使いの仲間入り？
Now I can join the club as a mage, too!
There are limits, though.
制限とかありますけどね。
（山本）なんに使うの？
んん～→
What will you use those for?
They're sort of an insurance,
保険みたいなものかな。
計算外で動くヤツがいるし。
since there's someone who likes to make unexpected moves.
それで
一人で来ようと思ったわけ？
So that's why you came alone?
まあ…。　それもいいですか？
Something like that.
Could I have that, too?
What?
（山本）えっ？
バックアップですよね？
That's your backup, right?
目ざといわね。　でも危なすぎるわ。
You're perceptive.
But you're also rather dangerous.
いざとなれば
冷徹に撃てる子よ　君は。
You could calmly shoot someone if you had to.
Wouldn't it be worse if I panicked when it came down to it?
いざというとき　取り乱す方が
心配じゃありませんか？
（山本）扱いには気をつけて。
Be careful handling that.
では
作戦を教えていただけませんか？
Could you let me in on your plan?
（早河）
もちろん。　それが知りたくて→
Of course.
Isn't that why you agreed to come in the first place?
話に乗ってきたのだろう？
正直　こちらも期待していた。
In all honesty, we were hoping for this, as well.
最強の魔法使いに
最も近い所にいる→
To be able to work with the two of you, who have the closest connection
君たちの協力をね。
to the world's greatest mage.
（早河）軍は
２日後の１６００ジャストに→
The army plans to attack two days from now, at 16:00.
攻撃開始を予定している。
敵の行動を
分散させる必要がありますね。
You'll need to break up enemy movement.
僕らは
反対側から結界に入ります。
We'll enter from the other side of the barrier.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]（兵）
おい　立ち入りは禁止されている！
Hey, there's no trespassing!
What's wrong?
（山本）どうしたの？
（部下）民間人が接近したようです。
Apparently, a civilian has entered the premises.
（早河）モニターできるか？
あっ…。
Can you show him on the monitor?
真広！
Mahiro!
それ以上の接近は
許可されない。→
You are not allowed to come any closer.
速やかに退去せよ！
うっせぇな！
Promptly leave...
Shut the hell up!
そこにいるんだろ　吉野！
I know you're in there, Yoshino!
撃つ度胸あんのかよ？
Do you have the guts to shoot me?
こっちは　丸腰だぜ。
動くな！
I'm unarmed.
Don't move!
はっ！
バキッ！
（山本）発砲許可を！
（早河）相手は子供だ。
Permission to fire.
We're dealing with a child!
子供扱いできる相手かどうか
すぐに分かるわ。
I think you'll find out soon enough whether we should treat him as a child or not.
カチッ
ダダダダダッ！
むちゃだ　あいつ！　うっ！
He's being way too reckless!
Where are we going?
どこへ!?
逃げるに決まってるでしょ！
We're retreating!
We sort of kidnapped you, remember?
あくまで私たちは
あなたを拉致したんだから！
バシッ！
ぐわっ！
≫ダン！
（山本）上!?
He's above?
ったく！
（山本）あっ　ちょっと！
Damn it...
Hey!
吉野！
Yoshino!
大丈夫か!?
何考えてんだよ！
Are you all right?
What the hell were you thinking?!
ぼやっとするな。　こっちだ！
えっ？
Get up... This way!
Huh?
（早河）兵は　撤収させてくれ。
（部下）はい。
Have the men withdraw.
Yes, sir.
どう思う？　あの子たち。
What do you think of those two?
当面の目的は同じでも→
Even though we share a final goal,
見えてるものは
相当　異なっているようだ。
we see things quite differently.
そうね。→
You're right.
It's a gamble to see if their assistance
彼らの協力が
吉と出るか凶と出るか…→
ちょっとした賭けよね。
will ultimately prove good or bad.
なんで来たんだ？
Why'd you come?
なんでって　何がだ？
いや　だから…。
What do you mean why?
Well, I mean...
いるのか？
えっ？
Do I need one?
Huh?
理由がいるのか？
Do I really need a reason?
あっ　いや…。
Well, no...
俺が　お前を救ってやるよ。
I will save you.
≪「俺が世界を救ってやるよ」→
Just like when he said, "I'll save the world,"
そう言い放ったときと同じ
まったく気負いのない言葉だった≫
these words were devoid of enthusiasm.
何考えてんだよ　大事なものを。
What were you thinking,
leaving something so important out?
ふわぁ…　悪かったな。
Sorry about that.
あっ　いや…。
Oh, well...
≪どうして　真広は
僕を疑おうとしないのか…≫
Why doesn't Mahiro even think of suspecting me?
≪それとも…≫
Or...
（葉風・通信）
随分な扱いではないか。
That was quite some treatment.
安心しな。
約束を守ってもらうまでは→
You don't need to worry.
Until you fulfill your promise, there's no way I'd throw you away.
捨てはしねぇ。
（葉風・通信）はぁ…。→
本当に　お前は　復讐だけできれば
それでいいのだな。
Revenge really is the only thing that matters to you, isn't it?
That's right.
ああ　それでいい。　行こうぜ。
Come on, let's go.
≪それとも
ただ認めたくないだけなのか？≫
Or does he simply not want to admit it?
≪ありきたりな感情に
自分が振り回されていることを→
Just like he doesn't want to admit that he's being swayed
認めたくないのと同様に…≫
by conventional feelings.
((じゃあ　俺は
お前と　どうにかなれるのか？))
Then...
Could I be something to you?
（愛花）((それは
こう尋ねているのですね？))
So, what you're asking...
((「お前は
俺の女になれるのか？」と))
is if I would be your woman?
kimi to miteta nagareboshi oikakete
Chasing the shooting star that we saw together
Reaching this place all alone
hitori bocchi konna toko made kiteta
Hiding the feelings I wanted to express to you
kinou kimi ni ienakatta kimochi o
kotoba no naka kakusu no
within words
tooku hanarete itemo douka todokimasu you ni
No matter how far we are separated,
please let it reach you
kono michi no saki ni matsu unmei nante
The fate waiting for us down this road
is not yet known
ima wa mada
dare mo mada
shiranai kedo
by anyone
To the future drawn by numbed fingers
kajikan da yubisaki de egaita mirai he
With you we can make it
kimi to nara ikerutte
nee sonna ki ga shiteta nda
That's what I feel
kitto
with certainty
A girlfriend
isn't something you get
彼女って　欲しいからつくるとか→
just because you want one.
そういうものじゃないだろ。
I'll introduce you. This is Yoshino Takigawa.
紹介するよ。　こいつ　滝川吉野。
So cute...
His being younger might not be so bad.
（女子大生）かわいい～。
（女子大生）やばい　年下いいかも！
I had no idea you were so sensitive.
意外とデリケートなんだ。
A kiss...
Not here, though.
（愛花）キス。
あっ…。
Episode 6
First Kiss
（愛花）ここでは嫌ですよ。